freegames-24.com 2018-10-12

# Privacy Policy

  * ### Play Free Games

  * ### Play Anytime

  * ### No Registration

  * ### iOS and Android

Before you read this Privacy Policy, we would like to assure you that we have taken every feasible safeguard to ensure that your personal information is not compromised on this website. This Privacy Statement will govern all privacy issues that may arise from your access to www.freegames-24.com, or downloading/playing any game being made available on the website.

This Privacy Policy shall be part of your entire agreement, including but not limited to the Terms and Conditions, User licenses and additional agreements that you may enter with FreeGames24 for downloading/playing any game on this website or your mobile devices. The provisions of this Privacy Policy shall create a basic legal framework under which all kinds of collection, processing, storage, use or sharing of your personal information on this website or the websites of its collaborating partners will take place. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy shall apply to personal information shared on forums, social media platforms, and other public places.

Accessing FreeGames24, downloading or playing any game being made available on this website or the websites of its collaborating partners shall be deemed that you have reviewed this Privacy Policy, understood how we protect your privacy on this website, and consent to abide by this Privacy Policy. In case you have any hesitation regarding the provisions, please contact our management to resolve your concerns. However, if you have reservations about your privacy, even after our explanations, you should stop accessing FreeGames24, purge all the downloaded content and discontinue use of its services.

When you access FreeGames24.com, download/play any game being made available on the website or use its forums, social media platforms or other accessible sections of the site, FreeGames24 shall be entitled to collect your personal information. However, this Privacy Policy will determine exactly how we collect, process, use or share your personal information with our collaborating partners/service providers who contribute to run this website smoothly.

### What We Collect

We collect your personal information solely for improving this website and providing the most exciting games as per your preferences. You acknowledge and thereby consent that when you access FreeGames24, download/play any game or use any services being made available on the website, FreeGames24 will collect, process, store, use or share your personal information which will be in accordance with the site's Privacy Policy.

### Identifiable Personal Information

FreeGames24 will never use any kinds of automated tools and techniques to collect your identifiable information. Personally identifiable information is not collected until you volunteer this information when you submit such information to download/play any game, access forums or social media platforms and/or subscribe to any service offered on this website, partner websites or the websites of collaborating game developers, distributors and service providers.

Accessing FreeGames24 or using its free games directory is voluntary, and you may be required to submit certain personal information such as name, age, gender, email address, location, and other details of your demographic profile for registering/subscribing with us and using our online games related services.

FreeGames24 and its collaborating partners, including the games/service providers shall be entitled to collect, store, process, use or share your personally identifiable information when you voluntarily submit this information for:

  * Use of our free games directory, community forums, social media platform or other accessible sections of this website.
  * Downloading/playing our recommended games or using the features services.
  * Participation in promotional offers such as surveys, contests, and sweepstakes.
  * Registering complaints, receiving support or providing reviews/feedbacks regarding our free games directory and related services.
  * Requesting any - game, accessories, information, feature or services offered on the website.
  * Using our customer care services to resolve your queries and concerns.

### Non-Identifiable Personal Information:

FreeGames24 may collect your system related user data (referred as non-identifiable personal information) by using automated tools and techniques like cookies, log files, and web beacons. These tools and technology allow us to collect your system-related information like browser types, device, operating system, and Internet service providers, etc. We may use our cookies in combination with log files to track your presence on the website and the use of its resources. The cookies and log files prove very useful in analysing your browsing behaviour like how much time you spent on the website, what type of games, accessories, information or services attracted you, and the features/pages that might have caused you to bounce off.

These automated tools and techniques are very useful in managing certain internal processes for evaluating, improving and maintaining the features/services offered on the website. For example, cookies on FreeGames24 enable us to track your presence, recommend the most exciting games, accessories, information and services as per your preferences, manage your favourite games, streamline our advertising campaigns and improve your overall gaming experience on the website. Once you accept our cookies, it is not necessary to repeatedly enter your profile information for subscription forms on the websites of our collaborating partners and game/service providers.

Linking this system-related user data with identifiable information is likely to enhance your experience on the website, FreeGames24 may use your identifiable information in combination with system-related user data, but whenever possible/feasible, your non-identifiable information will be used/shared in an aggregated and anonymous form.

If you have any reservations sharing your non-identifiable personal information, you may disable our cookies by reconfiguring your web browser. However, you should understand that cookies are essential for accessing this website or using its free games directory and related features/services being made available on the site. If you disable our cookies, certain features of the site may not work, or you may not be able to use our website at all.

### Use of Collected Information

Please acknowledge that FreeGames24 collects your personal information solely for improving your experience on its free games directory and offering the most exciting games as per your choice and preferences. Therefore, nothing in this Privacy Policy shall prevent FreeGames24 from collecting/using your personal information and promoting its business interest by offering exciting games, accessories, information, and services the way you wanted.

FreeGames24 reserves a discretionary right to share your personal information with its collaborating partners, licensors, affiliates and third party game/service providers, who make it possible to deliver the requested game, accessories, information, and services. However, FreeGames24 will ensure that no information except what is necessary to provide the requested services or comply with the relevant law shall be shared with third parties, and when applicable, all personal information of its users shall be shared in an aggregate and anonymous form.

FreeGames24 shall be entitled to use/share your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To recommend/provide exciting games, accessories, information, or services searched for or requested. FreeGames24 may share your personal information with its collaborating business partners, licensors, affiliates and/or third-party service providers to enable your requests in a hassle-free manner.
  * To follow up your requests and get your feedback. FreeGames24 may share your personal information with its collaborating business partners, licensors, affiliates and/or third-party service providers to ensure that they take your requests seriously and provide the requested game, accessories, information or services in time.
  * To send alert notifications regarding the new and exciting games, accessories, or services being introduced on www.freegames-24.com, and inform you about new features or information that may help you play the game you are looking for. We will also send emails/notifications regarding our policy changes.
  * To promote products and services of our collaborating partners and third party game/service providers. FreeGames24 may share your personal information with its collaborating business partners, licensors, affiliates and third party game/service providers, and allow them to send newsletters or free demos of exciting games, accessories, and related services.
  * To facilitate third-party distributors and marketing channels. In case you give your explicit consent to receive third party promotional offers, FreeGames24 may share your personal information with distributors and marketing channels, and allow them to send certain promotional offers at your registered email address.
  * To improve this website/free games directory and deliver an unmatched browsing/gaming experience.
  * To develop our business relationship with collaborating partners, game designers, licensors, affiliates, and game distributors/providers.
  * To research/analyse your browsing behaviour and optimize this website/free game directory, or consolidating the usage data for internal purposes.

If you do not want to receive commercial emails and promotional offers, you may unsubscribe from our newsletter service. However, the Privacy Policy shall not prevent FreeGames24 from sending alert notifications regarding: the most popular games; new launches by game developers and gaming accessories; information or services offered on this website. Further, Freegames24 can inform you about any changes in the process, procedures, and policies for accessing the website and use of its services.

### Sharing User Information

FreeGames24 will never sell, lend, lease or share your personal information with any third party advertising company, do anything or engage in activities that undermine your privacy on this website. However, it reserves a discretionary right to share your personal information with its collaborating partners, affiliates, and licensors or the service providers. FreeGames24 shall be entitled to share/disclose your personal information with third parties under the following conditions:

  * **Improving its Services** : Subject to your privacy rights, FreeGames24 reserves a right to share your personal information with its collaborating partners, affiliates, licensees and game/service providers so that it can improve its free games directly and help you find the most exciting game, accessories, information or services as per your preferences.
  * **Fulfilling Your Requests** : FreeGames24 reserves a right to share your personal information with its partners, affiliates, licensees and game/service providers so that you can receive free games, information, or services for which you might be looking. FreeGames24 will ensure that no personal information will be shared with third parties except where necessary to deliver the requested game, accessories, demos, information or services.
  * **Business Promotions** : You agree that FreeGames24 may launch its business promotion campaigns and sponsor surveys, contests, sweepstakes or other promotional events in collaboration with the game developers, distributors, and other business associates. You may, therefore, be required to submit your personal information to participate in these events.
  * **Direct Marketing** : No promotion/direct marketing shall be carried without obtaining your explicit permission. However, if you consent to receive promotional ads regarding the games and related accessories/services from the leading game developers and distributors, we may share your personal information with the direct marketers and business entities. In this case, FreeGames24 will take every feasible measure to ensure that any advertiser does not compromise your personal information, but it shall not be liable for any subsequent breach of your personal information by third party advertisers or direct marketing companies.
  * **Third Party Service Providers** : FreeGames24 reserves a right to share your personal information with game developers, distributors and third party service providers for entering a business collaboration with them. FreeGames24 may also collaborate with payment processors, survey/contest organizers, newsletter providers and other third parties who contribute to run this website in a hassle-free manner.
  * **Other Conditions** : FreeGames24 reserves a discretionary right to share/disclose your personal information when it believe that such disclosure is necessary to: 
    * Protect its business or legal rights.
    * Prevent fraud or illegal/unauthorized activities on its website.
    * Comply with government regulation, statutes, and court rulings, or cooperate with law enforcement agencies.
    * Facilitate merger, acquisition, or transfer of ownership, in whole or parts thereof.

You should acknowledge that FreeGames24 will share your personal information with its collaborating partners, subsidiaries, affiliates, licensees, and service providers in a responsible manner, but nothing in this Privacy Policy shall make it liable for any subsequent use or misuse of your personal information by these third party service providers. You should understand that third party services are governed by the terms and policies of the respective providers.

### Security

Your privacy on FreeGames24 is vital to us. FreeGames24 has implemented every feasible safeguard to protect personal information, and will never hesitate to do so in the future. All transactions/communications have been secured using industry-standard SSL encryption.

  * FreeGames24 will never ask for your identifiable information unless it is needed to fulfil your requests.
  * FreeGames24 will never share your identifiable information with third parties except where it is necessary to deliver the requested/ordered products and services, comply with the applicable laws, or protect it's business/legal rights.
  * FreeGames24 will never store your identifiable information on its servers except that required for providing hassle-free transactions in the future.

FreeGames24 may store your personal information on servers located outside the United States or your home country. Storing information on servers at different locations is very useful for quick recovery after a crash or disaster, but this practice also creates a risk of uploading/holding your personal information in countries/jurisdictions where security regulations may be less stringent than your home country. We will follow international security guidelines regarding physical, electronic and procedural safeguards of your personal information, but you shall bear all the risk that may involve in uploading, processing or storing your personal information on servers at different locations, and accessing/using our services over the Internet. FreeGames24 shall not be liable for unauthorized access/misuse of your sensitive information in any manner or under any circumstances.

### Third Party Websites

FreeGames24 may include links to third party game developers, distributors and gaming websites for providing valuable information/references related to the gaming industry and useful tips for online gaming. These websites are owned and operated by third parties, and this Privacy Policy will not protect your privacy on such websites. FreeGames24 will not be responsible for any harm caused by a link, banners, ads, etc. that redirect you to third party websites. It is your responsibility to review the terms and privacy policies of such websites before accessing them or using their services. The links and ads on this website shall not be deemed as our endorsements or recommendations.

Nothing on the FreeGames24 website shall denote that we sponsor third party ads or endorse the advice, suggestions, offers, demos, free games, and related accessories, information or services to be featured/published on third party websites. FreeGames24 has no control over the contents of third-party websites, and therefore, shall not be liable for the damage or loss that could result from accessing these sites or using their services.

### Policy Modification

FreeGames24 reserves a right to edit, modify or replace this Privacy Policy at any time and in its sole discretion. When policy changes occur, we will take appropriate measures to notify you about the policy changes, and once advised, the modified policy shall replace all previous versions of this Privacy Policy unless any part of an earlier version is retained.

The participant/guardian has the responsibility to regularly visit this page and remain updated about policy changes that may take place over time. Continued access to FreeGames24 or use of its free games directory, community forums, social media platforms or other accessible sections of the website/services is deemed to indicate acceptance of the modified policy.

**Thank you for visiting our site. We notice you have an ad-blocker enabled. Whilst we understand that you dislike advertising, please understand that advertisements are our only source of revenue. Please disable your ad-blocker for freegames-24.com so we can continue to provide you with free games. We greatly appreciate your helping us in this way.**
